[{"topicId":"7","id":"7000","langCode":"vi","question":"REy4vdSgrCZ2uHF5HKOIsUSjPXwALCzGnOuA40Sl57+MtYlP4AOLl1xh3d8dtwz/7uEpX/GIKmvIpjVCCjm2gg\u003d\u003d","answers":["between","at","behind","on "],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf1fwoNw6nzE8paXEXfNJvJTfKRMyGxQkSDYX9pkb22JPz8M31JvB0MQZlBDhEC3cQ0geS5paOgYw28Kx2nqAJGn374bkG50FKvXvDqwXk/cJJHs8r3iLVbdM3N2z/U6Zc6bPVgMacskpRJGv4din6bEYDPby73u++LFx1eYWaxrAzTrCcRRPjl4Iyi8emOVW/Aj0PH0H8URjHFrF+EJjCoQge7yUUzz9R9twjgo2bMnUG5YyYsPgAg/IXBR0pF4qPBfTIHipwxxmNEI7/p0YlxVqjMYfgN6JsTCKYat8vIa77KOzEWcssuuJ4oI8p85oozgKGSQc0okDI2aQwABp7eeZUPxt+ycInBjHxZpybkq5VaHkYriC4UkRazikMdxB0nXO3g/+ksF7BuIuxX50CPMj8ok+fNa2UEAZ27T/T+Oo4VC7vjINdGs2OkVoI03u2o2vioiccjDnLxQZ4bnO8c9slAShey8Z3IrxJ7m7iDvzbZZwK2UGKBqwkI49WrnICn5nANq4FSlmOGlzz9sjqVJvXH09KdP6NqBWVUAIQHKz0d52p4fqwAm97/BjnNzfRyA/5TL9+cLqjmPY3BxEpkicoy9DFL0JAT6c/cZLCS0ofQ7Lg12ErqjOhhaNnQ8sNnrojboHBGu9ld2ZoKQEceUZrvKp519OMgK4bdUuURhhsB7qlBVIO7vLX6TamDbp23eVAWcC4Wqr2PMsKeV7+31bCimoPWMDsEfwp6qpzLA5CMjhyaHdS0+JOHPjPIdB8Mo7IrvFnHr9lIECiooFXPALBPdgp+ILNlzdZYMhGklO868HFcy1YqujEs8QAkzSvJCyPDiPbdYrKY71WF3JE4i1A8R89Y3IM3Ikae6WB6ckkOSov+ArBMESFYxeBypIyV4X2shd/Mp5tZnC2kRYCjfnEI8DrYoBxg0uHuTCV/5BKh04J+YJTeKt4hYJklVE/XKpY30lPQX6j1dHLZ5nE2wwR9uZJG2IiqfsKrovSN0jVTFl2iKsgzIvQAKNejStUag71A3qwsRUwDBAuZQhKwh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8U+/p2u5A1+RaqQcTXQr+sQwwvProtmdFlZBlrERqVr7vj1A2Kb3S3+DbCnj6PqXLlVmBiaJrZx/N8JFvDOn7tb5jNYV3hd21ArMqrj5PjWlA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7001","langCode":"vi","question":"bV8rYTwM6z95cijcqoaLFRXwMMFvJ6EflXj5ERv0AhSHVBylAbkZqfzxLUo+rXClG5Z+IxKUeLrUUXoQGeFr+g\u003d\u003d","answers":["along","in","after","opposite"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdPNxez1B4dr9usLmdPYjt8hBxeXB6szU3PomDAEjv3RBYea6wwBDoY6JUGPxIvs1wiII/g8SGvq1myv42YlYTKR4SmOwu6MS6bCxMMJuAE5ShvTc/5TWnURTbsccjXt1d0pIFaNOtywyNBO59WzXEx7xVTqisAGcg7Ri/BTQcvmO++vlmK2xBSpJvPWTTSkiZanKxtD1QtzDK1i54N18Len19Z1I71UnH2pFLTkX8QqOWBIgdD8YRVWSdEKMM9oxQwheWsbaHnTvFGdEEaASJYuIPMJxdGAwmf0VB3s266lGdvBtdwPcLmFkuc8eEeC7+xSvWCR/V/epzmweEcwUGzRdOStFvZZYxXrPwmU1oKciaXa76oNnxwDsBxcqyaFyYcQQlCPyXZigUcBBbZUyGOhy2ZwYLq9jpVACk9ul5ad83RYNYi+Sgc4QBk/9KDf1WnPR2ZHHToKBzWNAMYASNW0q1Hr4uQB+G3gbil1Yi/PsCCs61f4T4M1RK/0WCKmDzeDdDSp++bCpIKCts3O8X5VODmKqf5cIQY7fpotkwtZd9PjuCXhbkhu9Y/H4+ttOw\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7002","langCode":"vi","question":"PUkftUcRH004UQVaiCxjHh/7jTwwG84vE6/2eBndw9za4TXkhIGIuVoQ8ucWR+8UYQVOP8sCHOEJ9Zqpn5+eYA\u003d\u003d","answers":["into","in","at","during"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdPNxez1B4dr9usLmdPYjt8hBxeXB6szU3PomDAEjv3RGQevU9GmNiF2zW4zamgbyXMPfYvWP36EQ5WSpL+KxURLxLFUSoPl33K1RABj6Ai63SkgVo063LDI0E7n1bNcTHnVc2A1SD6asAZ4zoqt3BxgGVazDLmEdTIT/EgNcxXwTCdgNFx3UhxyCR0XikOIo9aD4+sdY8p6Pge9qSkNHK6rX0uAu/UAbAP/m7O5Y3LL/zN+qvUCEwysY3MhomVeos/5ftZOQVzIxkgR3Or+H6nrXnzwEVTiSr3JPcwUlYilEysQuk5827x7aPhW5jmCwca6r3sVu7MeJpTJfjKIgD4FUyNvE/WOxxM2I4aCTnVO0s0VLd+8y8wiasYYFBNLL+V5i6tvzSYuTnLZJlIR5RCxs1CR0MeLDapOM2vuKgZ1zBJwEZscXyxLTpdUeWyBOlvZn+0rjNiEMazQ1EUn5fQ80xUtgEb9lwMVbxlrEnjZF5hYgG9d4MJB/kYuo7HH+TjnAOvho+VpnAMSz6/IXT8SLGzA/EOlt72AR5EaBLh+1nGD+lPdot0CB5KV1O3oaEDyxT9T0cF7st87y/ySHmIrlbpFWBxB2skyEBedU3QBulxVoVk3Vv+XoWeNTSSock\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7003","langCode":"vi","question":"Va1WYNy5IXBKuwtvu4mJibsoPDZ/1QWyR653OlMf+F9thqTCd68uyGFNrKsmWeDS","answers":["in","at","for","on"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdPNxez1B4dr9usLmdPYjt8hBxeXB6szU3PomDAEjv3RCjU5jYvBCc1LBZGbHFtqOUonxEDyRtlNGh35kYvsDgTH61yjdtm3bzx/NAz/RHQNqraXiUtZGPXxcpzXU/FXYNpraT/01/RcsGl6eMpYeGd0BeuiOSmlvaBD4CAHa5oPAnNwh5dzrXC42zAKop+RAXAXW0Rx9AQGmi/fGj0/gBShj2kmnUIvNb11kJ59x2vEobCdBtdrYR648H0Fr8qAP/hr9MiHvTW01vHLo4vpjr/rg6DMoXT2KrXTLDA7XftfEo4+JxgxxiUO6MkAFNCyH/JWCd6yHZjaeJSp5BV6M7oJ+2Gs64EXkVzjaFKi4HPTIkDuY90qlK3PR4Hh9/PfOtiCOcyiJxmvvqtV6cGPXHbqth1t2oWZVIJAidRC1cRWemC0HIaVypjLO/ECZMh59dD9+J5CzgworjBEsKCIH5phGg4D3HerStgtJ4Dpr4OOoCyFBtWZhwhPZnyfWYN5mmqcwMISY/BhGJcxzzu4SJBwF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/Fwd0kPPe+18eV4GebG0LTdx0QqvO8d6VJTtq+PvTlb44rInwln/Z9oT/B+kkmTthif9CYQ5gG5TaChnJU83z9HtZxAcEf6czs05PuOdJq3xA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7004","langCode":"vi","question":"eKJ08tYWEDqlm2/hOHenONBP2LoPzSluuBTXoZ56WcxUOxPOR+3mi1maCuDKyfhMinQx2ijC4/ouJbP/qqekGg\u003d\u003d","answers":["among","after","with","on"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdxKai5QQs9sSwhkndgIMcuhBxeXB6szU3PomDAEjv3RPCmjKOtcbjdaGowG8V+05VtMzlBWZ9oXFqufAFTNzlHU910gxOoWH2yXN1s1JbMCdS33ic9viZe0XZWbIrw2vUbUcRG521gT5ilk1xxlKFmKvhgBm5xISaqENJbXJmE9VlcYR42xzvl57nDfo1J+sO5NXkf66X0YNi6cXoRYjSwi5f5lJmMJrTdJj9VE4LmOGeuiNugcEa72V3ZmgpARx5Rmu8qnnX04yArht1S5RGGGwHuqUFUg7u8tfpNqYNunbd5UBZwLhaqvY8ywp5Xv7dmlaYCQXs2Re9TvgAlO4zfZATjhSlynTBh1n55V2R+1uiQcsMFA4p3POPJ36b50mZH/iXYIveDNL7ajLZOR8klTP9SZh9VbVNNeAMTlKIisZlRCZ04qIijbu9MyHPKORupkFMYxcNnBZOW2EetwLqam7d+8VcpjfCIRlhsbeOUwbrB/pRsOpG2KYsAJSmQARboWaq1GQCJZW8mB6xyfX2uU5qd1wBylxEVEQ04sr3s/xeV6PEtEb9JogzalERysWby42dsuuKZrJn3krU0bhdZXdfLk5Ht181eTeJXNZ8UQJibKi7O2WcG6CzTWnkn9snFDPE73ccQShC6w30RqeUvnQmweQGtK8HqeAtLozQkgcMKyKmSetsKbuHwkV7NFVloS3OwM/27aceSTBX2H5DFiolWY397MtRmfawZPVBRvQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7005","langCode":"vi","question":"R/+bv8WQQv/6tqVa7vhDXQHBpJEwo4GHbi/cPfLkj1dUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["before","during","until","above"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYc6xbfvCVF5xGNxfx3Shzru/mxCPyoQlSsQLkNtG1zN6yRLZccZVzedzPl15mGrx9vjcz5lsr/eAO8VAf0qGsHgxRBOMiHai01T79qjfJsTN7FlyeTVhlJeovK9R/VGvkS59fPyYf+JKJyvEv+WdoCN5Ubggm25PGFOG5ul88RKrxJR9KdQS/jyouFkHJDuA77ElNLLTOS7s/f+VM5KFB4geB1km12Tl20k2rVVXpQMqGKr4PGpU/IIwQlsxky+04yj3j+bePF33M+bdZ6couqT4XmlHyGf8uFbGqFggvP240G5YyYsPgAg/IXBR0pF4qPBfTIHipwxxmNEI7/p0YlxzS7bBFLL6pQ+3+E7nydlsGsPEamOd2cCjrFMv8p1eTOw4JNseyhPWxpwNGyvgiz31r4bHOqqtjH4iWaiR1oaGPJ0509iX78dPPXwL8eel9wyGBXt2a4wSexh+AGqp9KnRzNFRKgnDNOBq94UFgFDgl6MF2e6bEzvalGB/2V0p7lFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfSAbkSwHV8CBRXcQCzTW6LFW94DPwCr5Yb0jA4a9MklfGhXXKWw6vQLL1lsraLCJ3fjf1mld8uE8XDz5OBscwYU\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7006","langCode":"vi","question":"tR6fOZp4rEWpukJUtRs8BtboG//1EhSjZncy3jQrUdD3jZG2N3GNdlHWHjSVbtF3hG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["below","inside","behind","along"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBY2FQZqGRqPVZ8NN4eSr7T+rVLgVKqeCX92qiQvEMbg79IwtKmgw4Hgn85UftNt2sOBt5YsEsghu9To5lAHyvpel0MJpd7DSSWHUUaA8rHdguuCLDm5gnmoyLFmR97yN7B/vE/bQLPO66vZojLnXiinwkFRWXswSaXToAVPWPEcdWDGyzs+kKvbDGtI5S0mVPjQ+dsSC98niay8ZbUj80TmNFf9I7OPmrXUe0qQqrmL0se6fA8629TMXsxDgm1kWBnz7h3xpQvLJm2PIehKkMxtlU6CDA+aSszQbtXkzDjiylxFDyXmEAPxfvhSi/AxLrG92BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30xkibxB1zgGy2EBpFBK6JEyaFcPPGJhjPxUFOsQNilpNpUcpT+K/T/10CUhIe2mXsIJHNZ0dk7qwSvT74/5MyAjah7IodUSx5tSEfZvmrz+mA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7007","langCode":"vi","question":"fhsVZH5Q0yjSg4J2tL4EzghqpEaX9a1Mg4bXkDd7+9UecDL+KEc5C4r3kx0zf2cda8rt7ewhGGsh+oQThxobgA\u003d\u003d","answers":["near","across","beside","by"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYd6RHPOUwF736vFpNoukbbKrVTyLy1b2umI3cdJKauCkquHLKnwm7F9jmTo1MPqcIA9a5aaHPBHOi9Qx4CNEwLXwMHrxVcTn/yiKahg5rW1pf1Teymbc8aNjVYbZxo6tEPcNirJVPJ9ApTzenXu9UPqZk65UYdMEpRfvL78XvlpDFOZ3ICbZpcs+gcVjVQnE5Dvpd57lHtW8SJoocAd79MtAl9ogtU6RJFv/SGEA3FvDuEHqz2BrmBtpPCkIJDV4HBNcJjtS3ay3j6A3TFbJA7w5xSSTen6isxYY7SZkJClZnTLShHWm3F4iyu0g3rZSNzYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdveUy81cf/xh2faRjj6Fmbh3XObdNd67u0+oyGvDU0wooH2jt1skzdq3QH+64lDOL7LKqPhsjh7z7op7OVOgj8tu0kdrVlPcLIpgTIgC9wWwaqApaKC0pucSWAkYc6J+x4"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7008","langCode":"vi","question":"gZPaucJjrUoAoct2zDwcVajGLNt31Zi3l6qFgvPw9fjJWzifvR3OX0adeLaUX53A/fixW0ZWCDUkO40CkzgqphjFkpid2EGQwy9rOEWUGu35iY2f3UxI1mGxSoVZ7x3F","answers":["until ","to","with","by"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf1z7vuzcP1yfibXFde2oatGm2kxUXNLBeEusF4WDxslbzZrV+vidSUaHpwrWZJDmf4Rj+cUbCraav8s11i5CysdBxM2LwYIdCj6e5W8UMvBG0nAKQ9tmjnHFVi5ToCyjl0D5bsKps/A1Q3dTAtdmn9WLrkCh7A5xXUKVqX8Qq5hDJ94vqThmYjTlwc3TKiEoWj08gtCY//1G6dZVidIrWrRzNFRKgnDNOBq94UFgFDgl6MF2e6bEzvalGB/2V0p7lFJ8UsE1DvDNE5l0y6ejhk7oPVX0Gw0pUXhutpdpTOfQe0e+shUSpgA80QwQh5sSoiCU461/WZQqz32rzrLl/ZOGPv5Iu+u9ux3QZ3ClbhdY1gKrQadgIx4Pn4xXtXLfdJfFXxeO1DrOvpmJQsm/5NV/h0nHxzGKDO3J5E4SihXPR+hoJUc8MTwA/aWGKiYYE\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7009","langCode":"vi","question":"3wPeR7k+d1e/PSgVQHKvZDHh8wrmUQ/sTa8hcvWrqYVektzgVHs8SzGdrQ/WPWdMZFZh6fqsfRbXbRA2mMFtAw\u003d\u003d","answers":["over","among","across","under"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"UvKRbRQ6zANLORdhOmFZb+ijsIjo2sjgdm/JUEhpCxhrLxQgGv1Q2SDKbcCNyTGZWcReIauAJ0+k+OsqBvxBFOkCe2EJg6DxBP2TD4mwJTtTK3he7LToomzW1eIwtqPZRnmmZ36KONQH6EjGbUsWVzrrcWIsOQYZwgj1kIiXzzElZhmTda/66qiRD59f6RWweMplWNb+/oHoK9WkL7ItpQbAPN3Lurunh3J+F3nM5ozyaglK3cDBECDDPm6K/1Ff8zo8prUQdqqqKSZfF9WIJti9dUTHNI3VQT0ts5iDoWVrdit01yzMoOpt9Z9Qff4crn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9iQCU4ZyfZ87w9aUdrPnrHtXq57PmOTUO2P2JTmy1sp5XqnP6AYHYv/N72S567fIUE9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsOCvGd4UcRxonkrVfIZpgVlFNr14S+xyeGHlykHSzQpveqOXJD8tlhmSKudAONTAPJbmc+7CVdNTHcpROpXK7PSJDicsyHiq3nvErOYXI2/LWBt8EF3zSLV8r9vkJdzXgGijYueAgIUQStGl0TrXW/X4"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7010","langCode":"vi","question":"oULUFiddDM6UTdjW9jIE5fAJXKNTOXM+Rg35lQ8zN3VwEPy+z1+9UfEH8IhjRbhLfPTCyeIUIbopiCyzuQmAEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["by","at","since","in"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdPNxez1B4dr9usLmdPYjt8z0WPbLTwnrJEyhGsODXJ2vgW2E6dxPHmA9emtv5YkkassLDx6CFP+e2rNaaYF389yj8fJnKxeiaB4Ylgv9CwfPXiuiJ6hZdu+kPvBhf1jmaNhyrlefjvk8vebCkyVvg+KWCyon2GXFoEp8oj4I1lUiJJKK+VIW+VSjqqWYm4Vmca4jFPRzO+AYXOGOBgOTXsjBCzoD6rspJryflHGxPemCKCMH1YdV6rNIa8ot2G7kYViDDxUmCd+L8lPLxqrZfCYUl85twRj5HkOY0gIc1OwVHLIn5jNxDsm5bfjvx1cX/AXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8cLUMXWAfPXUXeVRlWokobtpTWX5kjUQCAtA53pk1jpGfpY8nfNZ0IuY3Cn4CmNZ3B/nOfBbyx8E0Yfq25VvFvH+qsA6IyzcYvt/DcwOFdm2cLrvetgcobcOclKmntSWIQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7011","langCode":"vi","question":"xukWGiXn8xZacXJcdNA5FD6UM4Nm4rhpFmmA+HyqLJCGoLgUw1wsnSyJ2R9Mys6SB2OUvgiHrshL37MV4Wp1fw\u003d\u003d","answers":["in","after","for","on"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdxKai5QQs9sSwhkndgIMcuz0WPbLTwnrJEyhGsODXJ2jId432StRI1LPJMVUcV/5A43mv9tc9XnTWqb34VfPJqVHsESZ6JfQ97YmDeE/Pre6KD4fmBST8TzKoTvueERZL4hUDfTdnB4iPpBlVY9EqdbL00WHwjh3mYHHQnH10rIwbn6oKNmBwdVcw7v5hJzxxj3o1pH8ZHUBh75W1l7HAE1ikAFXzQkbsGb8nptwooLQ1uZXqRJFawzNKt6K5LjnPygNOmUVeMbO86Cb8EUgPd8uNnbLrimayZ95K1NG4XWV3Xy5OR7dfNXk3iVzWfFEC2RW2F5ugIeBdz4UOrNElQWjgW85seV10lWLeASaPHsNL/KcMrBNbSsaYbvBiaQJloiPB+DMyOn4c/Fomoq8LXkHz0XO2ERYd9bIM1WE1SbQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7012","langCode":"vi","question":"ipWLWJ+6Hp5tkb+i53yGPBI4Rk2LF/n43i30Vi7AEUt3IPCTcjluvGjJ/WJfejjK","answers":["by","since","for","at"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBY2FQZqGRqPVZ8NN4eSr7T8jPdUbU0I8jh/CEWDPzmioFmpmWaViUUF5RJK3LEk6LNFAjGNqpoaox8qkeoxkHnRtoYnEOcCsxcgA4rPXsEAXYnEn1FXg03ei79yhWZltqBavB0xUAt0SAqWBV2HUVZpTsw4P5ST0lOc5QYWDmuIQM2+xfx/TfgTN5wnuovwYKu9NWLq10Cpo9uyBq/wI5Si5V9/vVsHl5kws590r7+Hw9Jk8kynMxR+pZUbrvuPzLRV4QiBhJJbbzAfYEjFTNmlQYt7nF9/wXCw+iHRLTWtkxc+IY2nhy/qhzYt6JZbpV3yhEVgr7w6qNR7Juu+/t/cG5+qCjZgcHVXMO7+YSc8cY96NaR/GR1AYe+VtZexwBNYpABV80JG7Bm/J6bcKKC0NbmV6kSRWsMzSreiuS45zgg6UOrXOv4p77q34xJueMZ1R89IoTDfcXMp2tdnG3hQXzzKbBtSRFCTh7TWZUqUOd4VYjAdKQAAqclcIZmQTD76lGbZg1P+agsgqBg++3gzAXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8Q4ZhqHwlSTmFZ+RNxcpf+jngokrwxsTpxvI4YxLBkU91s/TKf6lHfJ52+D8U3Ad4hvBVu0PCZfwhfpqyUEkjiE\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7013","langCode":"vi","question":"CBtgwmjeHiDPLySiScuPeGdrpMwcOxm26Z9n/Px77HHPfnEuLY0xrEFWiErmC6ET3Ypm4c+2WaI9M3kMfrKDOw\u003d\u003d","answers":["about","with","in","of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYc0/wC/502NSvOoeMdkr2ZV7vVjs9ZEu6m+0nOpSJza+3drHRxEg66LMctftdWCro3x8bD5xfDGfzoDL/pRz0YWeI79QXEfUQ8VEK0esar7WjgOaQlgsCZqmnlz+i+qvRg3lARefD6psC+oVRQFB3jjMlakGWLVpTDEQYmMVJdBE7ykVpeXDBvyzZbrn8Bg3xubNRNfM4UJuuWp3lhqPP68ByXiD9iHjZKfY1Reoal6lFDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqeZwg8Egg7r6ty9miVg2rSXB2shUb7xi7TYgleY35hc4knbPyU8BqJqm7Pv0Kt6+V7P/Q5xZy22EFO9GeyPe951CLlu3aM0KctviJcID/cleEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7014","langCode":"vi","question":"dweJOHu1WEF+XI6SYyz7rYhuKhTa0+IVurGNLxWqmW/OpxlhklmlI8BG1/vwFrPDk+Wb4oIZfk8q7QxsexHEQ00k4zNzZtejpZPw79nrbtQ\u003d","answers":["for","with","to","about"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYc6xbfvCVF5xGNxfx3ShzrubTznUlT8y+/y57FDxsLZ/9KgvxSNPV/4WDUbNVBTL0loI43n7bSFxph8Aa/4+omBXCwCJCQUSefD7aa9IEqFHaOJSrTbpSARMb6HnwyuWs+hnSFWJ9Ex0qbqSSoVfLtctAEns7O0sLLZISxHi7RCxhGgc8UtTFuFG2JPK7NDcn8tYbVgwx3E1vRXDDZW5VqOtsPwTwWyqek7DyZoK5/p65Cb/ROdXxvCRjyg8ycBKw0k+bYXCES+Bo86xxFlkpgmt/s6TjG0C8BZd1FVmP/6PXdX3zDNKBcjEJVWrze7Nv1p6MQ6m6zYIbsV1oX0aGjeXmFiAb13gwkH+Ri6jscf5OOcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPzPS6h8iszCMDcxM3HslB1gG7q2/DzEyoHIDATsUzHKyVOGcWPz/r5aP8hOn/wZf+0omDkPqSQN2Vs5/ENA/2p99UdWr/+unf3MrVbL2asIJd3MOiB0IqAUErb+CayW9GJJ9H4j2RbhyVyEIhxXgfR+JwKesrccq2zqjwwFbvHz1xTR30Mxf5+CU84ga7wu00U\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7015","langCode":"vi","question":"0wNS73rqqsQ8HZM1NBMEeQXg3ph7R71n80WFWz7iCXcxXTKiDs6aB3t5vdPfixwk5VBBDb3SbPYwPIMxcx1oDgR2KFA8flsRikG5E7gLxJk\u003d","answers":["with","of","to","at"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf1z7vuzcP1yfibXFde2oatGm2kxUXNLBeEusF4WDxslSONZOPxana0Ppzfks5BfTdU8NuP1FZWsW4QvlXNkEGHCeAQH+KuZc2BSPHnKR90M4lT+ttEZnl9OGARu5KYAZgtiJMfXs+eUUw4z4TqJQShJaDljfOF7f0wZ9K8JpYI1M1L6EIUjaB5sLsxnnPZOG2EaDgPcd6tK2C0ngOmvg46/sOB9/WA93+K/HMvweCpLiybkAvS7/1EFbkLqMi1kwk8ZZ7uReUrx987EsN4BUGOGJA9jDp91TvDFlVMYCHJcDGSEVBSoUd/FfMI/ka52/CiVM1nIDq43aj9mps0hfYUJW8ezKQit9zEr/u7XNvH6UIveGlNLyQ+GgwPBY8D362aCxW5vsUD7rlWNSKVyAmBWKr3bUE8RUCQK77QN53ioRHvGJ8lk2+nyhEWE59cu1fYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdvHIOj4O/Hb4lvSTrY4xaYBNQkeeavDZXInEEXKOIhNunZJabhTZ970F3Q+T/wFYj8c26xgFJpLZPXek/mWdTPnZIeArlPsE/S1EmRe4nfgzd/vK3G+eFgTG27NkEC3gx1"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7016","langCode":"vi","question":"4dNW2sh781vL1lHBJcaitB0qRzONP50JCEI+bBpLlHNdy1zh80aBB7Nd3Mj5Hq2q3+i1JHo4Yd4hbsFPGy/4UQD1KPlfuSPbDyqFr8uhgEc\u003d","answers":["with","about","at","among"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf1z7vuzcP1yfibXFde2oatGm2kxUXNLBeEusF4WDxsld3LnmW/OCuaP0dCWdemba5U+JsVbgjGKGIzb8d6qLyXvvhyVYIlm8ZPdXMJ8au9I1Asb62Sn89vMGiWH2qgW7GYCrtPunvnLJmKiO2r5rjmp+BJrGEihyTR3f6EpCnhnPFWoNWNIyGlsvz5tB2Knh+YpO8oWyOl/0dXzOssVPObn8lF8+Tn9XWCRHT5bsZYcRZM2+1MhcAV/3G7AzkSThmWz8WBM8VguKDhiQEsqYHW1kcIdVpB2r7Fvx7O0lD+s+r1Xc3CYC3oA8VLiJU8EP5ZTxORUAAHPXR2HP9h0LuJbOWmOoaWIAY85xENucgmulQPmJsf2JuNI119h3xQX0nJ0YPW6hGHTorTJmXM4IkDM5ScEibjXES1AMrOn9Gf98yiknyuYQQfQPgkiZMU6adjOFYNoB7ZF/+MWLUc1ncqtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7017","langCode":"vi","question":"S12hf0PmaEjGAmhO87/uk+mnps9Fd3ZM1LSZixmCzOGrRKnVnxswpkbsx1InYMbLkD3Gfo42DjPNLSRJ+VELqGjHBaDySyyN2YiKlZAREDrv08fwm+pLlI31zWBtrbxq4FI+fRQsGodQ86v1bvJnqoRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["with","about","for","by"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf4xn5kY0XXjHXKF8g0me0Jb/xlveWLq6+Q0wxSDFdj5UvTTyDwQy1wYvzwbrbb+vMH/apx907NALUBbhdNYCCEeS3gTTf0NP9GoBg2akJ0TqXa/ZEVMDFmeBJuJMvu2wTIUI6Ml5s1OBeegwrIDP8OVX7ZPXm1IXyY+P7yk4qVuwOASnGIhaJ7c+KvrBZk+ELkXTwA2NOjSEBglgYPjDDbp+ZwDauBUpZjhpc8/bI6lUv6wAp9IP/Dxx7L+jxcZa/oWaq1GQCJZW8mB6xyfX2uS63qeJcRlLd/E3C+sfVXscfQnbw26vhqAjD/CED9FQwg7GtchnN78UfE+PO8sPjZXmFiAb13gwkH+Ri6jscf5OOcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPym/GezKimh+WSf/wRu7o+L/37Ypjlc8eq3JpwNBlfHFMtVOMuIaxN/FWdRT3+2DdPtEvneqhThuIJRXxU6UZnwNUMWzwnIWrab3t0afIdTd69OTHSAZoO521VigOYhkxSrMo7JVJDfuzIvqITNiNFRMQb738QYhIIZzy8YAtk1+mFqLONztirItWcI67N2V5B5XWuOw78hH/gCczEBf6PlnSgzk6b1QTCJBCRYTwH4P5PuM4RWeOLYvg2M4b+7K/I\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7018","langCode":"vi","question":"z4H8ePsgrndXspudvtv9rRxNKxrYFCZF0BTmMdqVNzHAUeIgHN+II4lkpQ4inW+eDLfWlgnD+YtuidIYW9AzmQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["inside","toward","about","of"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYc6xbfvCVF5xGNxfx3ShzrubTznUlT8y+/y57FDxsLZ/43GSRck8K07Djx+DHaYq5OU57tqAayfsBZF3RWzaLPKhma1c3lQfEq0DLFmHZM7yKgBV6DQyxK4fLh8j5LstXUhy47QLEhGmQZDHzelTe+ebfZ0ep9JHZB1i7XqYRQ2qZiTRzsoiRY0lxjUFFn5mldanzb+cWUjZeY2XGWzDE7Fw7HOjffGAqQ17zdolXSRRYf4b+Ngcsc1ki2x0YuRK+kf2sHGk0HlrIoSgqqiZXvFUJOSV3yvpEMb4dOVEeX+YX45U7B24Jz3OsLiLquE/8yMu3sUxPnJygFgxw1HuMzzWgHD8qkm45lrmG5xORJ0hAg11r50q7WnwSlXBkZ3Tkc\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7019","langCode":"vi","question":"iiEhKe3eh26/QYxenlmVScBhBPo5jrcBxl4MTDiaeByZU4BXHx4+ja9qEtuSAY5pujdHyKqflFcv/ovHhimXyUwOuE3CawVCkMNSJg9hDmm3BymO91TzEfI//uxANDqb","answers":["for","outside","along","into"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf4xn5kY0XXjHXKF8g0me0Jb/xlveWLq6+Q0wxSDFdj5VmivbTWB/Q9W58t85b8LeNZvjcK6p6/lZs3BLc2qjiqOaafWtsYMYUjXZV/QQgljHkt4E039DT/RqAYNmpCdE6l2v2RFTAxZngSbiTL7tsEyFCOjJebNTgXnoMKyAz/DvHibkB4LYdCvWsfUtdxs1fO7NAXdWKVsySswptCkJ6lUYWbhnyRbr/Mw63vplDeSWIVuMvoUiV/04wg3de9eVsgcQrpr8/78IKlVnxCKY4t/LoLR65DMWsbOpNQFTMzTDVq0QHvE0ey1G70AFN9J8po41iEnrfImFnctS/YJGZF2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb5tQBbHmDT76hHlA/k8NEY+/IoevVxGK4mXXDv4Tm9+VODrPgcBMDAw09ZUAYyptVfVzaXcN0U/gYz4CzXu2SSbo5OGwQ/8CcP4rYaGOOCiRm4eXCQP6ntPDobtHmmZ6e7Fdbe2eAAStPmTfhImjCvpBiceVeTWU45AtNrXzgKwt"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7020","langCode":"vi","question":"N+xXt17Gg6Q6l223tAaxi95WdTYYzGrvJxiClSXuFGzVY8gL3kZ6u+m6oPmzLRlqzFOzZBVhSFWfBq7h1ptnmQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["to","during","among","between"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"F+3tf0uZKXOAq4Wb8fQU7JN69vImmALdnx9sUvyHBa+q8UnV9h/VrawZWZzcY3ussMJcf8OJYc15LXy/mmcrGShe+V+r+5DHm66a6FQB7hwMkYKT1RRm6BxGfnraB4SRiWm6LQ5Pq8qJxV9B/wLwnuFJVYONZYgDfwj7/LKHbfEMGJVvD2pRa9XFNthSji436UFivbxYUARW2UBzHmwmJSedgvdn4GQxYZiJf3AR0bevIaXCXJweAxudqUhFqeOOB8bJz5+RFn0mwk40hi97rMwgL/1YlkywTp6v5kCk/xlQ9yhCTmkvgEdLhHPz8zViMFjhzYgp93ekLa4DqfCyMG/Y/rqwpFuXIF5t5UeGAjP9p6b3QyQX/CMJ/OcSVwSVeDbuqcsb5S0kawKkDlr8RamQUxjFw2cFk5bYR63AupoR8JG5Tzx6g92yN6/vi0lnj9W2v3D2eydZuna4optrxE/hXRthiHI5epjpEa+yx/kxRd7ioILtLWVi4kxlBQvGPH/ek9Hd9sEYnTam6Qpt7XCCQ+9UqNw/Rh6WumJtIxUWzGoghj+qtsuCX1H2+tyKCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHufkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYduy/LaufRPtLHnzLbLBGSUQ6X6YgORrA9qUKghz3O6qPLjZ2y64pmsmfeStTRuF1ld18uTke3XzV5N4lc1nxRALIU4fKT2DsTHnvrUjYhJsWWFhSbsmidEN50LUN17fwXho/PkXa1SbdXdDTLOGVNxOCO1LbgsxiuVfNvKen3nVsgwi0WjP9wX7nzqqR4xnjgWuMCjssNCR77qkNUJpGRi6j2UL1emh/dlr+05cevkDSwTKjFUseYyShwuJ79mJLA\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7021","langCode":"vi","question":"N6kK2E4GZ98iCd4/tcVYlQGxT+vgb2XrSeWeiPEfUUab0wTFYiCDgsP/MRI6uFHpQadggtoaE5uMCFDXkAQqpA\u003d\u003d","answers":["among","between","toward","across"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"5ZyrnLiDa0PJ+yf9ZNdVzOfkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYdrDlvrETaLDhtCZ2vRYs4XM7QKfKVPqoI9bA4Bk7IRNhtcbLrbGSbncHmD7RAJr5BGyu7avctN5lSIVxdY6Ftyg0D88MO9ZbOBRLJ4OM7vOw1xY4hezPgBKrgenlV/tY69GIIroY4oXxnAADOwv4BoYDoB1cE8urT2/5vnd3h7Dn4HDwseu9DrBtWzlAQwV1cJM26vZ5AwnYRsnuEJ80zr/wPyLG2K9XlgHBTvA4sUSgl0+4EPznjUDqjvPJhY7CnUdWVVejC5w4s3fGZRw1lxkGHOslLKQmrT+vhCoxwSbLrcuB+zVzXAe3I01G0RV/fcruJ+3qF9k04ZVgrd16y3fWiN0MVc5sq22Uxb99qnpqxKNdHqaZpOefwtuoi8JKgW/t2C44zRyFROgt2o9O8v7Gdp7vflAt70oBlP7AjNu0K6jzD7k9qilrJrKCqKo2M7ZxN9iG37TQdjg+vZXv2FUfEYDJjtkpMvuy8+wEDhwuuvDm4xp1gGd3fDM5zEpHu6bDWUwPzcMbu5uZBuW851ErfVq96WaDPP5Yjk+yOQ7E9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsOCRXx6EYVz+iwk4ZFRkwNl0Nb94rJ4lGs7G4gVxOr8y+qcXkeu7wiJgr9phPconN9DS6tLieLOEwVDuv3LEmvZq0SgOGbps08hRU6CSBJ1MH0483YtwBk3ll2eBQNx7g7mT7jOEVnji2L4NjOG/uyvy"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7022","langCode":"vi","question":"/E1rVFAj7TO7W/hLBr5RgKpFKKzgmJ4b4+hdjNGY7sF8Sd2vxOYiUqvLENMxhZ7ojXI7bMbmqZnEoHljkDkL15IsGw7j4o6uWldZDMG5Qy0\u003d","answers":["during","between","to","toward"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"vzE/mhe4Dws81kHph4GjHsB9QfjWQilM1saX/aotadPANkoZDXzwYvIMkxBF0VhNJIt/5OEdgiVyk2Y9psSwnljYx9wMNIzvNJQGKBESfj46bfWO4m60gzzbLsbeA19XBPyO0gAqttomsglZEGvmC/rQKQ7/ECpBPh1xZPYFcVPIYu3S4z3xQ41PzTS1VL/q9/CLboUuqJ3pXnritkGbtxCBhAkICL3DRp/lp7U5uhF+tRIHHanfEkcHP1uBSzwoaGp2cgoeyBU9hA1IWC1+mNbS1JycQlCFIWIUch4RMkGIQaRBpL8zb+QwFQsaXUxCdC3b5hFi621ZPObY2EeHspcRQ8l5hAD8X74UovwMS6xvdgUd6daGfU8Cry6ic99MZIm8Qdc4BsthAaRQSuiRMrfGhXIdrB77qbVCXhDAQAi3VCOJn8kKfhrD04Z616iGSm3hp/cFausjxV+Uc7aVGb1r93cZuADXBPOjPiND9Y12qivdWGTpnWm9uV9pnuMCEPqG+tjnqnaq0tGvORv6nw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7023","langCode":"vi","question":"kSuo6Ax5lTymEb1qrvsYm4LC7RAwZbkEBX2A3ErbnKHhELL8mRPru9mnQSgaZkLvfayg5CjYj7A7eWy8gQo4HcIMv08irNq9+xohKbqemaQ\u003d","answers":["near","behind","between","opposite"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"rfbHMVm8FIod2SBfB+uGNdMdji1SBCrptpiiGpBT5W0MT7WSlWIY3N88Rp5gnuqnBWRCPgjE2i5vqGYus0vUrk/hXRthiHI5epjpEa+yx/kxRd7ioILtLWVi4kxlBQvGPH/ek9Hd9sEYnTam6Qpt7fUnVYQNrvsoesiFLVKyPwvJUbjn+Y26UBOaKQ0n3Y82v2o80u0ICZDxpanXEi0B3gZLJPs3XiDURiWYb7Y7icydUfPSKEw33FzKdrXZxt4UF88ymwbUkRQk4e01mVKlDm34jiuqDa9GDhJVZ3SRLDfQUY4ke2VHrC7pfIUMwFoo6vVdzcJgLegDxUuIlTwQ/llPE5FQAAc9dHYc/2HQu4kaOoAD37JILKlNoMRGpzHMC8L1h1S7PADpDArQqB7POU4M0NS1AGhW8LNDaoodhIFw4lxp4ohno1xr9ftM3a8rVpawHLW/McnN73Lqch+po6BBwJBmtgl69Yfp/xledLs\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7024","langCode":"vi","question":"7RrLNo6D4SDlwm7eLrkmUtatlJwPIV6j4ljrb6PHMEPFm1YXPwDG3lQJmvR3D6nTp6rsPFLwD6I69YOiNrrRMQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["to","opposite","for","until"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"vzE/mhe4Dws81kHph4GjHuY1YGMFtA2q4GXR2frVTy4mzmHwvLzDQIduEoOV/W4sCOA1ahfLzRMMbwQkAlkAk019aez6ZdzZBqrGifA6pBoEu3UEpqED+UcCRVBr90GZpY6fnEebApW+hMIplbobQwoAYISNQPUIHb3ZLuZupNWDlZsbPqgRd8b1klqXn3Xk6S+gbOZfYVILgUM25Mhiu5G9J72lgbeIKbnqjZzv8ZTbKsjiTEcLSb1mo3gqGq2tVeKYpGIOWVa9IR/nwKznwItX45cxEqbg+dTCCgROCzQ/DF9iZOZrx0YuVHgaLt0C08ODLK7eZzqY3t8siEka437krmMi2RgXNe6L9Tt/pO5Dzo0I1aoqOS0nZYigciE/AFQ9a606F6GwnEfgLWMctOfi2/ecSWDhyhcZFJeFGfud1C1Y7vcLZQKZSN86a9zc6pAzKXS+qBlnJ0sQ5WUVzAV0p0MZzF1mmKVcPQ+VcEQpLItJhKwIl/pzfg2VjWyYsOCTbHsoT1sacDRsr4Is9zsmExOlg+O+dQMVANul9VE5HjIfiwErN5vb3Ku2AFt5RKMkdrHSIyOB3h+RUc5v43HFYlus8+qOSeS4Ufa0EZ9QnbckcN1JRuyqT9H5R6L0YKCRVQ4d4jpqQoNjkXbdb8h5IRCxSbFiTxgfOEXTVyVwfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQTOIrNt9I0fD7AS8dF4jIUE+I+xxyZgUaUbKKVX64jAelKVcw+5FaFPiLlrJEd/umPRekjD/VgtbERWsdI0BMdbhmf4Joel5YjO4FZbmdsBoUaUszAMSm1O/NufX3NO4l"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7025","langCode":"vi","question":"kBlbpBFpnT4eU+3q45vl7+T6BI12qSkiKbFXMECdzc66p1s1q3sjp1eSVoUWEKyM57///r8lLLYrEsPuqrY73A\u003d\u003d","answers":["for","behind","between","before"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"Kr0g565jlod/zXliiLcdfh8oLlTv1X9QFCA3RJfOVMy5w1uBO03RhAQtlWBKAspde2fssmka2VsEY1+2hHo9ogQI7H/wE3WMKuueNYxoUQgHfzPgbPAxNvLbXqWpYEQLV+m+wF4l08a80mMw44K/85Xn2W6a44yq3x650gBdXajp0f2iK6pUEGCr7L7m3ZugzRqUTyxm8y7PBRPzn0lOGagYLqfvo2qIgccOPkIaZn4qv9QkPLZ3JKMNiqyylzj7zr91AS1IKeEi+yPMKeWUN9qU0NHcinp899Vtdv68rIGH1B7o1NHL/doyxA+4N/Xf2g5szV2RaOAfE6NHpsY3gmjmPYFSSeErFqKej6XhyBc5t0xNvASdCJfdlmVQhLAGjDcD6u3bdLOhXyN1xMcL8kf7z2/tH5M0ED3mUyXOdv5B9XPIvSMJctrRHvDnx5FcPvpdMsWVZqPi3xQv8VQ8JoBlWswy5hHUyE/xIDXMV8Eh+8X59RTsyhTaKPfRHCgUNPkNTkSZviomUxQ661Kn7t1NRsliabdZpoGmTvzWtDEBMeszVUZP01DMBpkiD8LQJddVjwd6bsJraPJwAQ8a+Q1tnEl5/9EkoxztLBNqjgBoUUbpmvaMJi1eAnsQdqJbyUZsezPz9qsBh6vBalL/XnB8xac44f3LANp55pTArFDF6jWud9TaGQ3ET3Z6HwJI65ABLXPK3R7KYfztDhPflEKFicoEc0WkJ59K0f778LdabWL+DZ6FizRaHIDkbTnN0XPPwkB4RPvP1VAIvP8Ql9wNdyCKxTvPVZ9J1KsgIU0\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7026","langCode":"vi","question":"oDmVHhBwXYHGwYbRkGbMalP+s3CFshSuE+7Tw7iWHb6zE97HguAlSctfrWnmu9/3G2ahmAnS4n3KK5KAHJZR2xTWtOyackLzpuB146Zg5HcJN/fAmGZouOt3L/PFSg58g7gQTuFE9q4r2VJNjBZc3w\u003d\u003d","answers":["with","in","to","about"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"BtqwdOfqP6cKK64Trab8mzeOqXWHPAEe62Kd5MZtmP38gqAmhpZQ0Bz5CsBChrQ5uxtSt93cBNd52LSMeCzySKOSXRO9RiaAmjnvtRGa3CMwsfG+7sIXeQYdYgb/UFQ4njxmjIxRdyJwtovGwelN9vRI8f3V8Uf4j2KHFds19A8Ddwh5uL2stOmKS5kmXF0zS8zPRmDrfWcYcQ8Sw0vgU3hyLpnjUJQtPH9y67Du6BRslBH6trvQ3Jkb9gsz6QWV1tLUnJxCUIUhYhRyHhEyQYhBpEGkvzNv5DAVCxpdTEL4h8snNPatbEkSluu7oyu8OkzWydm8eDNjWkOOkf9oS+OcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPwxoTbFRn1n/7PqQHaDUDbnnGWFc/oPpGDbWV1M/+DU55rWt+2Z6nbkAuQ3ZVClJL0\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7027","langCode":"vi","question":"ZeiYGhCt8W68FFfA8x/JTDQ6JzG6adZMPU3EbdRjRRSu5VxyufV/c7OFa4Gky0MEVnYeNAmu3tiNrTL98O3EIw\u003d\u003d","answers":["about","on","of","in"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"cdQD6qBpQaXmvf5B7VPPmT9QstO2K3ZVhDjhFHO7WBy9HjFOAsTKra6L1ovQ8jgpoSpXZiP6qfhBSoFRVxXTgHRGnUjKf/ahQSm30V2vb9mXgtsDTVuHqHolRSzsCk8bJl0ErLv63RJhyA1Q6azagX8Fz9r/kyr05fvFfOnK6CsrYiVfh20jrB9jjNYWXQFm21l19ayGuzgrVSC3AZkk98z8pgJJeR8J9/07hD+wy+MO6MxHTBJW0+zrY0xJJKqexozWnhT45O8daVUqDUoJ0Z9unlN/xlcILlrh4ZWu3soeNckvq34e7iuoPmUewvyy+pnlxmJP0EmjjUeA9H9dHH7sau1xQXvUFGEs9qo8jZTSrzZwMDSl7NgUs9evXfbZxc8/e9JBi56GEeFmgja31JOEKxPf15ZtfxvPW1Q+Rb7djBqFl+RUS8KFIUH4RJ9LPM1q5Vcilqcq0RbsejFrM/BnGtwqY42UyCgyDg1DeXcWj4c8V9cgjDZ/W/k9rFeyCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHufkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYc0/wC/502NSvOoeMdkr2ZVwX3w6MKFXZhePJvaBkZ389g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2/QX16yGQQiVI97mHLzGtwSpHZGPLRUxOY5NDYcFCoxY425CeiZwJM6OI8/cywr45kCDFS12o/Rr9Ch9KEwBGE+nYI+uF0ITiZECT8jizZ1vA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7028","langCode":"vi","question":"+VN2DGd9aMaHGr7dbX9RmQV6uzzPyKvzCUr0UCjcR1girreiiw1KV01w4UuEZZLjAbq6xiAe0y0AZOC/9SSeqQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["at","towards ","between","of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"j4DH2p03k5EGrCbakb8RFkax6TvtHuJ2Ox4ds/GIhUhReZkP0ZFZY+YTE0JGV3Ie+I/6wL7hE3bpvfy6ejHP+TTLBMtx2XLqO8EaMwA68tDxVqDVjSMhpbL8+bQdip4fhTS3zp9rS8cxe5PMU1F7sHqfy7oMF3m9cK0pHgdNMKtc0vL6+1JgTXsk3LcWtiSOFfO17gF1ThcmbkbiAiynYaYvdp2oqpwaZw/aXHIDSzM9a5aaHPBHOi9Qx4CNEwLXwMHrxVcTn/yiKahg5rW1pfiytfdq0wD8/GS2N5mb9E/yPs/CvgAjS0wpi1Y1d+6pLoOpzQgcdYAFx/X4AOwFtABfi5WSXYQr98BqQj5HgY17AWqmdGwZJjbNbwzJmlXXw9mnQoQitBq6mEEJkdQb6WU99PdK63075yJn/hk3TQkJNmokzeB6zok35DmN7hRkeqR+UgyiZww32RUCnto/+m5zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSgleC8It8zCF8aWzvujB/eB+/0ds6IXE+CbXh/ecBxLsKlY11bZCBsYGhluRluxFY0LpPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDgQN8TdBojLwoRUQPww6RRWNeqVfwxXzJ12MepKRL7M28cbz2Amo/pXxifBgFsdznDd4ClrSmUYP3lywi6ApNyo3dpFSF8VZZscdNuR7LK28F/9XIykZUDxeSv4wLLevEQ2phBYatAOUvD1btgjIxAZw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7029","langCode":"vi","question":"VZ6cxoLax83eql1Olw3gDaB4fWNiA4nOAxpurdpq0b2Wa70USB2Hmwuj0O76EogMo/2YaftF/bUeN/E5yWfy182JDWjC0F/k9kxDxUv/6MpUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["beside","after","about","in"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"j4DH2p03k5EGrCbakb8RFkY3M7JmhsEJqcMfjy0e9EJYl8Gqosoh0kQubRGZT05bUVLY1yFXVLsGu5jYOTSYiLG4AJUz+TUwZiL9BS9qy51UiIqQplQV3APvwC837iqGZd6VR+FmNhjF6xRtKFh9uW1/t+dnAFzjRsugY9paPPpb4qPcXvybmr7lTiKCFgxJruhHO0sZyGQ5M5P8Bg8KOCjndnswWyzXwKiyTT3+ZS+MycE8PEkAEqj77mU2h6EEpUIfJxrbEEFtN8uEvN8oewxVsW6QMrDLCJz8Px7IYbqnPR2ZHHToKBzWNAMYASNW0q1Hr4uQB+G3gbil1Yi/PmAlwd2znVW0ThsSfgoNuuwOaUFPMFq7oTXYQ1CmLqY9aD7FTBF4k7T3KOP54nxq3PTYQHfRsQP2NJ3tF9bUQghZbdSKK2znLPns3DwXihl7xnrI4j2dstbmJd9RsxeoqaOeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7030","langCode":"vi","question":"TS08SClv5bY+x5dk5lm2a5hMXF1AWy3KODu240xFnunJhOE+2sDhkP9gKdC9156wuuZYNoK+5R1fc2bUCoNaAlpljMEYOENuO+uNdvIncXhUgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["at ","near","by","for"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"BtqwdOfqP6cKK64Trab8mzC4GykwycdgkKsK5XP9E/3NkCcPHY4IkInFxK0XoSNifEWW5wWwaTrZu9jPH1IQ61FS2NchV1S7BruY2Dk0mIixuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasudVIiKkKZUFdwD78AvN+4qhhjbq+VNEn/auHCp8iVRSimS+4203FPShgYCkEoz2eTrSUuJRI0rYlqzYXlMFHN3IGoqa8AbGB8UtS2sXgeMlAVI3OAGVrbQOQHLlYc5te/lE6b0Ln9xqQCaRIFtPrSxBNDsfuqEb9a7lrTMg7GAo9hj3o1pH8ZHUBh75W1l7HAEBfFHBqRfCI5U2YbmxHYvi65YCgCxHDGWRvbVL0238MZW7ohfj15VLClZAGYHk0vu/1ZCDyRfLkCE8ZvBDbKD38meOBZrYMyGZbq/IwdapSfQF66I5KaW9oEPgIAdrmg8Ywe03MlAf02NlYk0Vga4teXQGsQoOFUSHnAF/TeaUb9F1ErN2N3jAuHb+77j9lKa/1KII4LSIqkX/F++8PlX3cXPiGNp4cv6oc2LeiWW6VdkW4+A/4bXZ/pmCdo3wOKAUcs+Foeinaqc0D4FUHuV92leCVSBWXXDsCV8HZ/a0aW5QYBkJzH+tXa4f9JM7QVqT0CHyp5wd56B7ToOtcSw4BibyR3tmEObGsBrCAnOWbMNUqryd140GMLOZcTeu/BKyTzyv3+bFCJXp2lFr6/ZcV5sTAVLmskGC0f2ec05PtRVuwEakU9/0mISK8a5psm0SBs2NLH9ck+BiAsqC/9U8NEO1FaAEKqDzd6rFDEdYeo\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7031","langCode":"vi","question":"Y5OqJP/KYGrIpmtc5BmRRAtqSwIpAJaNZWDkA5FZa6SM6Pcr+3uJLidJISQ8cXLSkywCUNNzCXFNiSar0rkAZtscgJ5r+XPOBGO9Rb5WcaY\u003d","answers":["on ","inside ","at ","for"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"usHBk5YdT1+qsrCq4raCaA3QYE0H0WqNvEAJCwWS3eN7n6MJUUh2IQmBlAOGL81lTmnzNQv/sHpnti+ZFbYXH25zcvhu1ulwjhxYwwlSgleC8It8zCF8aWzvujB/eB+/JKe8sWgHfFBA8wUgBqvlsVx0AyylZ7VCOOkXvqnhHH0SjsxN3DK7njAPtpV64/ZXqKKx3ej5IF41WPuyWZibeTssICeaVUSvzrk/MIj8tLmidVMHjEUEjLPIIVecbs5z3hrD8DxR60YxgrUj9hIylTt5gjyPH6sz5Xhzq1J+rqRrTkTu46442xH7OxSL9xcb1G+pHQ1ZxxjJxqMArjE+oGeuiNugcEa72V3ZmgpARx7BEc3C9MOoy/5b/5+W+PUc1bnlB8P62uxgc/oZ8livX+vzTG3O54pcsh54EKRyfs/Iqc8WJ31ZZ3t3/kHCp6pao9PILQmP/9RunWVYnSK1q/qjXfqvdvePTWuV7VFstE1TP6GfdY2GhaSTrduEgjjgcuwHP11+MG1VWzbtl2pmZjEa1oQOM32/FRl3sIPGw6gV5flhO0rHuGPhdP8mvmXBUNgXfEL0FVD9al4VLLe+JXQDBkzqf9hjLDNmQTAzCnRpSvKuqEVuU8/XuPo4wcTfUtpj28KbTxJnfg9eG/oMCN4NW71zoGH5DZ47ZHwsnhJX8c/KLgPFf5CHPa4vHaDMpfY1QUlyEx7EiPlhQA/5p3FFG+kKzn5aB1DDHNOMw6ZuurzgsalUbb1YVPXatAAmeoUCTa0nnyAqWB+DK6p3Ln4xGW9Kn/h7EkZdiNL6WbSh3jpeRWxg/sEjwas39l+MPmO7gAOxSItU2UB1YPPdHKRyiTegUK0dRJL6xcgYzTqp/CAp9YmM9Bd0a+DQojwBEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc40UaWDVglpto0yKl9pu7voi0TQy5hRoeLZrXv8Tk5Aecy93hfpxAUb5BlgAD+ZsgOyjl4bcEBUxGu9JbtluYnxa+peQy7hbwbocVvJdNdKyeimSP7lHdUVIQIm3Hvt10wSA29WwW9Itq8egAsY88ebP"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7032","langCode":"vi","question":"fCLyvb8KPUTxFnyEv1+nsvKPf34zEx7j2egoikVDo6O/h75lRSGsJ55DlIWJ/wEQB2XDw52gmLS16aqx59bRCQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["between ","about","among ","of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"cdQD6qBpQaXmvf5B7VPPmSEM+MT0XANKMnjKiDdb2gMr//9+uvhmb5wt9MR/JBwWRxPvc66YLHcZDGkjYAuWKXKL6YNIHlqd98gDIEBn4okSDXgzZi74mutHb5S8SWjaBPyO0gAqttomsglZEGvmC/rQKQ7/ECpBPh1xZPYFcVPg1pvZve+0/qK978l2NpiWWmbOp8yn93fmvniQz1KY6TkkkCeXknPKdNJHBM0b6LZe0AXCcUApJrZl+hW5q3DwhlJpPhNYsqv1CnZ/ij5WLykXKYhTYEEf4rbZqwCpziIYpSSLF70Tb0HPtnwqoVg+NeUdoSJwWaYjco1VHp9BIIBuV+5DnQGtNGmp4hKETKhtpcCQVSVtNBXdHSbDhdGqhSA6og2FkApI/eFTaOImoCUm9CA4AaiSwk74xXu6bNcJoMaXv0Bx6HxJw0DVOoajXv1oJQB/Url+38xgCD6ycdpIVrQ1ZQ4ctiaX25EMNA7o0DRf7TFJ7qZNXduO/WRi+1uryeZ8nVviYOIiFmvxZw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7033","langCode":"vi","question":"U5wMmsHHpSjHibKvyT5V2W1MnykH+aEysHyBtP1rfnZSeuQKMlEomzYLxrVSIjTr96Ze7JMHnkFaSul1HfQoBUh1Unj6nd1niCxoBWuj8ITPqwf571W6wuMDYgnbSbxy","answers":["of","behind ","to ","among "],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"j4DH2p03k5EGrCbakb8RFpOxTWLt2TJoLtt8KIVJxE8QQO/SsoBA1UeqkqCCJd0xsCIwUYKhi0KepHSh7TBsN65/qg5HWfDsyhlRJOp9gvYkAlOGcn2fO8PWlHaz56x7XgHi7U2ST2HRETWPHpbZ5I7aAGZqa83bdJm6GjzKmy7g1pvZve+0/qK978l2NpiWWmbOp8yn93fmvniQz1KY6TkkkCeXknPKdNJHBM0b6LZe0AXCcUApJrZl+hW5q3DwPqAdh60wXqFQwP3yGKendLneV7SZMjNI9QNiDMokIhzfuIjWqsy220N75IUqOzBf6lKTiYM8hKEXFxBSWWIFnyUm9CA4AaiSwk74xXu6bNcJoMaXv0Bx6HxJw0DVOoajU3FYQKWaMT0Y6rGSw/6AhiuaAyygwx4UE/lDH0nda/Af4SeoGYI2J/IVD7qA+jCpJLgpaFk42VKj4QUGhY3TZyFlpG0R12dpsoDc67nJfeYB1LGfIdKG363P2taCA/c6aIEwttKhJSDuHEUZ6omJjXa+KW6n1xrCMkGGLNF2kVzmFNpezze64TY1OGW4/x04"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7034","langCode":"vi","question":"x4IA52t2Uwf+Y0axKhiI8s4lWAM3pIb7TFCO6yR1xtkYWfNR+uQjRmNI/F5hAMW0G/nVcxLFxD5rHFkdjg3uMLamEAPAEd1NPRNfGlQ1cN+QYqGk/R3bBvBUYkB3ic20","answers":["inside ","to","along","since "],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"UFCJTYlScly5c2IWxMRPgW5IXtDazI5jVSA94uY2jC68NcLIVibfERnFgBQs2sGPOQg40foygKqCGGLFxZhA1Ozhza1O3+ta+GVp12D0CVMY7XKK7JAIvuYBVpMhYy4G5rROP74m6zDjys3m9b5iweclHqEPT9jM6qQnzrGTE1OMELOgPquykmvJ+UcbE96YIoIwfVh1Xqs0hryi3YbuRhWIMPFSYJ34vyU8vGqtl8JhSXzm3BGPkeQ5jSAhzU7BQSWBM45rMMeMsrSMnx0daTXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSCAblfuQ50BrTRpqeIShEyoQpu3yr5uHT53VrlcXf7Oz4UgOqINhZAKSP3hU2jiJqAlJvQgOAGoksJO+MV7umzXpDxDGxXmjDVUlpO1d6dZTosMNyTF7U2D8lEldxlNI9eEDxIxG7G60yHJST07Dm0kSSTBxEdNTOFBD8g2yR/biCAis1IvmkhE/wE6poxz6z5LCenQJ81bcdmIDuP5davESDrn8zDHGrfTtzWWp3T0KIdnuqbec43vVn6rp4h5IfM\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7035","langCode":"vi","question":"5Zt06w3COs3yjLnOFDjOV/ML3GNVG4YIsXe80O3PffCkah6IG3XZ13Ql0tt1UUiKR3lZZrEC/Tj1k4glpbC8Gw\u003d\u003d","answers":["of","with","in","about"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"hFHf3cQKhgBnqfjy7Dx7yyfYOU2y+2xLfDSrglJuc/7ZA7W7+dWPnDEvCSeKNwyQCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHufkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYc0/wC/502NSvOoeMdkr2ZVkMZDj5Z7W+yRWkdTGjRDwWnVzbemN0bpsj5CYsBqez62l3wehBdZGUsHRPS6OncAagpgssllO2sOP6v/6udtprMMxRFW6BSITb8aAE8sldFoC2wZJfOegEy+h5+mVLWH5OUvF0tG96LMY+cSGL+rIaFIEBfBTbBUHn4TNzfTIo+b2AKk2Zuhliv4FCed5k6YT0CHyp5wd56B7ToOtcSw4MV78BV0wbe+4MX7EoHqqp+X0UerqeIXtdMkUmsBr3btfFXdM3JXpL6vQC3s1bBWs/sorqLzvzx6MY1IM/oDDfiSQLmLGkhNcMRa8yQn60tR"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7036","langCode":"vi","question":"LlG5lM6o80ke0WnGthN+O9EWKbPR/oLI6nY85t8JT6dhZbdeZqQzD7hkxZXetYYwqjZm76jVDbFh+eW6o7e2AlOjeGML1msUiFJ3kXQTNIs\u003d","answers":["during","toward","at","between"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"/Cgu3dmnWNeJ4ywiiBuacCd0Qd3vHj6iZG7hXsY5kIKZ+qhXb3p3Sdso/Z/U/AXbiR/vg1ANWBYIV99zOVzHqb1POXFjSG3ehNYRl1Z+i78IGihia11ICr1IwdAXxOEEV889Q7Y0Ub3piz8Ol86N4gH0JWO9RbukGIyC2kIOHbjZotccaVWyZwy/FXBIIxafpfnjLGPQ/jA/RyFzaoc+hgYCVtI9pf6Dh3Xs49LQ/pTVQbrWjsd7hoaWly6De9h5VN/DsVFD4DSGB8zzbDIfioU0t86fa0vHMXuTzFNRe7B6n8u6DBd5vXCtKR4HTTCrXNLy+vtSYE17JNy3FrYkjhXzte4BdU4XJm5G4gIsp2GmL3adqKqcGmcP2lxyA0szPWuWmhzwRzovUMeAjRMC18DB68VXE5/8oimoYOa1taX4srX3atMA/PxktjeZm/RP8j7Pwr4AI0tMKYtWNXfuqS6Dqc0IHHWABcf1+ADsBbT3hD1umgmxwbhheFSOiKhgCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHufkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYf1fwoNw6nzE8paXEXfNJvJwX3w6MKFXZhePJvaBkZ389g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2/vVV96ktDr1uG7V6Sm++IYsPoubh/R7cCeU6Hy1DeMXG89tmetlXKU4mhOUiKfwTE1XpiWmPiZrcIssB/R8LHCOFebHQwOJniRVuc8Y68XF4ZddLlfd4eyR0obJ+7vCrn8/v+5L2tfUVDAAfVO8Mn+"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7037","langCode":"vi","question":"D7vxnWhsYbLbwPzbPFuXtgHHkRv3mexOZVZ399m/dYQyz07PUSULMhDQ8bOyvDyqk31IxNcDUfOr76VZH/VTG/WoXhQwwQozXD6lnfQjY/A\u003d","answers":["with ","about","by","from "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"UyIP3u7OzMYVBmfCNsZOygtmrrFGjRkepqzJlenBWYwb9pzwStJkVkxBdAVYnZrKRMuT3md9yDC4VvK9QZBULXHFYlus8+qOSeS4Ufa0EZ9QnbckcN1JRuyqT9H5R6L0SPvrh4eV1vOP45fcil9Umy8AtF0MlHCpX49c91Q1UuCV2HwJnnvulbdEjZyhN/KxxviyX4pQyYVuKP5nFe1iHdx7GgVmJqoDVtBVniM1aEfl+sJQdVXpWYglLRM5FxLiY0Fv9iwFxTdviFhSKtJ2PAXrmB3x3bZCaa7SbuaDUwiYAb/Lg2Sbe9/fHkYyla3Y0jQTGeCoYFulMPDS3EpthJgKu0+6e+csmYqI7avmuOan4EmsYSKHJNHd/oSkKeGcOuTrPcCApa8PiRzyFp2cOr2rUdBnGRPTd1qJquzcU22J3qOV8wp3Rw5UecYIKHA54CP8zuf8cUmSL3gSICH02NoLrlU0s+t2RRGG74pInoRJqgSGInX+MjY6Y+mqWEm8I7qz/S/KK4cnAPQGOCXPQg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7038","langCode":"vi","question":"5SWRYhEP07OUt4ssGjs377TmLmsWptnKNbqLdbHZ1JK2Xyo/KxXLqvs5kchT77HgbU5G05RXPoLfCVIytWLQkXX2c5SGI7Us2FnlnsbEaa5w1Fo2o/goldXcyvGPZfmD","answers":["about","for","by","of"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"8k+Ho4d+/TufaI1N8bc1ay9TkXtCAH+8ZjkyLx+gEKEzJbVPERSn/lxcm8++g/gRoK6gaQTQRxj/UnqcIsc1Zb9Z+/9n7hzXktK0JG0QikXwN46Mj6u/jFbe0BVNhWBgV6benhirBB3Lg6fu8IFdRFfKTjYPpUui8He1mf0w6kVqKmvAGxgfFLUtrF4HjJQFPfcxB/iw/ybgQBr0oEmg8xEz7qrKx4LtdyPhDW/76IZjVoVzQ1HR7e+YNfev3COUMlakGWLVpTDEQYmMVJdBE7ykVpeXDBvyzZbrn8Bg3xsP3J0b72QOy/OTjIc1bth/JddVjwd6bsJraPJwAQ8a+Q1tnEl5/9EkoxztLBNqjgCOj82EelVPukRS8APypA1aEKhUjgxYaCX43AVH3+29ARll+ijAJe+juitIA+vUc41QD+64itaODmA1xcBrYePukbM0bpwvn3s3QADc50enxiLQyU2AHsjq8plH0dD9F27Vd1Prwqb0wcOqjxgFJ0m2kgdFfDHAqC3YkLSMn3nwNJdqUP4NNz5cKK7Qyp1284aMetdSSAQLren3uKFKRaZWwoAeG2dLMaz8SY58uq+lrLZaeZ50qJKgXi3pgk+zTq+AYh+MEkUpNFBQ27SH0XtN"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7039","langCode":"vi","question":"ZTJlH5xWwq125k5FR4Kz5I2d8g1JJkKfJfhm2QFptJT0Lr3TbXnN8Tp7nLWg7GPlGSWVgwdV5VNaTWKbNDwSzQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["on","of","about ","in"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"knHFckD04kBVk1lEbYIwwiNxcZ/6m+Hs2tbJyh3l7TP30sks4qyU3VGBInuk3PC7NeUdoSJwWaYjco1VHp9BIIBuV+5DnQGtNGmp4hKETKjbGC9SYnGza9irIVKx5wXYOW35iSaT/dAl3ZpEz5KaeDCx8b7uwhd5Bh1iBv9QVDhya/e4VBFzPweh0GGEpb2rneyePseDDkFAjGesv99Xmu++vlmK2xBSpJvPWTTSkiZE8s1w73s+kUAnbSLPaKpyg3haC+/HBpezvS+dhMWGhPilXWEBilD9J0YOPC3zXw/v9RarlecvBlIHEwN/Yor7SufGJe62R7U/SyP99fDv+4ZVcZrYZTOYv/arxKZdEts/ttrZWrJ2k4/7In2N8Zmx+NmOHxmFvUUMmqaqzUHmLesSkOEkjfEGEIMUSPLEpxu5joeH+RMEv45VhtSFEm5ZATqUxVD5u3iGtpxkc85nTBzLQ4OMhmwgmYkEsHo8nCDAgNvb90Tm/spl+/LFyGdSooPh+YFJPxPMqhO+54RFkoZmtXN5UHxKtAyxZh2TO8ioAVeg0MsSuHy4fI+S7LV1g6Mu/GEzIIK7qEJxo9qnxxCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HONkUI5ctwVSqVcwDg7Hx3A8JExKYQMJJOCxwyr396yr7PolGCabyg2PYyXvbqOgLAWWFDKFzDQiAJcZ8xQeLn6GZJV47E7SM+jUWtx8pnI3Aw\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7040","langCode":"vi","question":"7WV3x87rBgAjfeuVxDzCNUX2ZG0MV6W9HY9uOl4YmmhxMK6jZCLzi5UKpqp/yscEnWP2fRs5KKuS56TIacVnHg\u003d\u003d","answers":["on","inside","for","at"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"tWrBEkNGNrZF4wS3bl+BIeqfTP2UzuVPeQqKAOxGeIk3jfya/rQSB/Kg600RWJ5Yhx6eOP+2/lz+C+Kv6+QZREs9z9V5wQFZkiZeVTEMM46ggWlf+vUv7K/hDwyn87o9Mv0PMhOl0znPjFW4qzVYIapRX+JhS9QVA+OaZZ03yGGN4gVMff7Ow6S9xyIHdL0MvRSjCbJCEopY2Z3KWeHCETNvsX8f034EzecJ7qL8GCqP7NZ0u3ZD8BdZ/5Kxz9HJz9D4x21ITesJXtdXNNBX8o3U7kl7DM8MXwYDdfA10CgQh2N3VWYK8mZXZSu5PRl/sTF9XM+8fDQ+5hXxEPwmWoTyc1P+cZB1xs0RfkGBicNXpbHCzZRUsHrJWFLrP65ZEAsMjuhkQFz3CbFKqmewJqWKXj0fmVbD70bXl2WlYY3HTjcBYe6soF8NRNKAIHHa2bPUvq3Y5Nh4gQa3zQnRBglk3BH7wqtpOnF7e+eB2Fb0TBZqWqF1Hh9Yg9pZPg3MBvOptQ8/XA8BGm43OQd+PjI/KJPnzWtlBAGdu0/0/jq7XFa82sMgARWdyeId8BhD/4g0STDYlgo+4GYXlmmlroGhElC0XBpW8F4k56t/gZvuip0XBzACtgkxwKxrySi4cAVXebd3wMgYZlXVsoM7xY+kHes2UQGzWLUEj0kTHEeJbSuTQ9qkBXNseGPKlaSVzekaAkDGzsmF2TmbStf/wXw9MhRlgcs06qTis4oNMiI1gCaJ5ZW+ZDDLFRolPobUWFbzOvi9x5RRpENp6iIq9FfIRC9yUPOwT52mWv9Ac2bESQzbBeTpqNrV9EB9ITPCloRMzZvejxOzE+p8vIugcAsoT2UnmSha3bD5Echq1vnYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdv4am14kB0ycQDK+lzy6d4cD2GjXAjbE4L+gMva0EQRRtmmJUC5I/ME/DrwnQLrtpVtenUT+seW4hfng457xbRpSRc9zEPWjyG4+Pm/S52tfw\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7041","langCode":"vi","question":"s8CnI6PVqX9E3Ui4aj+d1oRngl87NxTrxoXXZybm39T+jF1+vfGt1ouFCyWr7+h10vJ5fi1AHDQStp01BI9fAFZ2HjQJrt7Yja0y/fDtxCM\u003d","answers":["by","from","with ","about"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"UyIP3u7OzMYVBmfCNsZOymg1uynjAl3vWlJXUpDnwh+yQtdu0+OdgSwegUpkaVKHvWFoxI/XNzGe16thmpk3r3ffgyYeDOaaAJS5amNq5a/P8fmUVpB1x9411KIIkQVywl3Xnh8tQJvxjKT+Lc7brOl2zypINrHniwK8dTZpccBQYt7nF9/wXCw+iHRLTWtkxc+IY2nhy/qhzYt6JZbpV7tcMd+1XaMXCTElv2t/uXBp1c23pjdG6bI+QmLAans+uFmBONxiD2ebIZ2MIDolTRBz2SRFFdIGVnQG6AxRf2MxOwlplL3NJ6KvgHjhtyTVQ+aK91rsiDjak7m2JJmeVdlO8Hxmf5553Q2wwmF4C+/IM8rQYk+iqtMLbsdj0vSW4Lwa5gT/YDC2drz+Ut/vnDrk6z3AgKWvD4kc8hadnDq9q1HQZxkT03daiars3FNtlck6fzgVLyGpqq7e3+YlfLAgtiqEkTFUOxi0aEE01AnpAdDszP4A0aEBnFg7xON6179e0l+4GiBHpJjdWzaPanLcwrSAHhu58ldAw5pGYPoXdJGq3SYQYXX7pNRWYcRX"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7042","langCode":"vi","question":"ohe/9/3bDjpBD3VJGLGmnFyUxKnaoF78pico7R8BAszSIjXhourWkbEWT8f/3DX4vBgKXfL2uSZelhJq9PuO2Vx60VYqw8MvZmGT6jxVJFE\u003d","answers":["to","of","behind","among"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"j4DH2p03k5EGrCbakb8RFh3weOPsQ6LsMpCXb+rULmulwIECpdV23FEO/VGYmc9JnVHz0ihMN9xcyna12cbeFBfPMpsG1JEUJOHtNZlSpQ666Ngp+brIweShIXs97i7CLs0DK+yz3wVQYlRjsVy9kBBp2naecSjDVvqGK4kba6pFWeYPMjTDtCU0+U81tAtSKnhVsaQw0A9yVvXoJvFKcggUyhrHWfHsP5mhsbEDmeWBwJJoF+nWdUFByNVXiXAOWDGyzs+kKvbDGtI5S0mVPl/qOf4bQLiZFbqGqG1ifx8AXEWnn4aYrRRXcyHJcCStuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuLyxNR5XzSOr7cHI4bCuBjLrtHxcVqbZztur/qZKORnVYg7faFUN8Map4y7284c4KjWvREQSPSF13qeP/PpBsqv2HFfb5ZVB7oUkPGMkU00TxLwby+S7sLWkNPGZh9WJD0\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7043","langCode":"vi","question":"a/KJfH4qWBYKIzkWyAbErOPEqmObV5OVkdL6GGqBnVCEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["along","for","outside","into"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"lBbGTR3qeWDxwijUwy6Lk7mYpPDalfjZLp2mYXYWSlpPfkaX+xSDTuc5Cu6DUZdO9UXwAHxnW8eYbk/RIcfAAO0Ou+FEFNvKg79Ep/5HkiEs4Pd4n5Z8clNfzt01Q33dHlzUzvOwYVwADDDqhoWfUaCuoGkE0EcY/1J6nCLHNWW/Wfv/Z+4c15LStCRtEIpF8DeOjI+rv4xW3tAVTYVgYN+I6mM4ocxk6X8CnnfUnqKm5YhX6CN2gijq6gRxKNoPgBzYGlLoLWqD4P7I0dYg7REQ2i1bUs2/5id22/RWhFhmGMHo9K/aPRq7HA0xbbifcJvIUR6GuuSczb89soSaN3yrXZU8FbCHivfULVy4lYu4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4ohXYHu3wLn0lUe/M126ID/TraO2RywxCuY1NEtObczWzLQhu/bglqXnezGEbLwAtVUUqV417boXhSdh8kvOjTI\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7044","langCode":"vi","question":"BLfvLCYgyV0cQrQfiUmVfoMStWzVvrHgFUKYHR7owm7MsWZLASMi5mL2Wf4XbRAXn6TCOrA00dUAG7L86zN8/BcpfAI/6Gm0NM9AZAydumbH4PYhjmFTft+Zh/63D1+QVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["about","in","with","to"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"j4DH2p03k5EGrCbakb8RFtPFiPOzJnjh3DoFVNW2eINUPaFSzeOX+Z3FuxflvJQRY0/vNTMs74iJNLrhb+zkd9lO8Hxmf5553Q2wwmF4C+/IM8rQYk+iqtMLbsdj0vSWJUl8axDcAorA2R2fVO9GqMi4cMFIhRuAlyfhpEPZ6UCYAb/Lg2Sbe9/fHkYyla3YEpa/LH/vEQ8Kbz+3WmlFMF6hKD9yjUkN5whX5ZnSstvH0J28Nur4agIw/whA/RUMIOxrXIZze/FHxPjzvLD42YF7ejZzlJu2NBLBQMRwdqe1GeSSK5/V94x6RZUXzHpDUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmp/lQ55MGQh7lC280SXPPo5jVseZDfttP2FtzMuAGE2p2hUsQn7JDjeW0+hgKF+0EZQ1gQPrfGulisQpp49NEzhkKah/EFUnJcVpUkInCE4L/fCmBG3gU6ZK+rsUddvrzzt9bg3A3/PZpwiDfEM5Q+Iwzb4dH8VvN4uZAerDSsImw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7045","langCode":"vi","question":"DupTJj8PkS2zdnZhviHhLUtKod6w3HjRD2SEMDjVdu/Z1m1CF3ol7b1iT1hTgIvn","answers":["among","with","between ","during "],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"j4DH2p03k5EGrCbakb8RFo00GFJmjzKowPM85GEcSsKaq0oJ2RrzvNkQYeTEugf+SIBemKJRkvXuFtWhGXTQwaPeP5t48Xfcz5t1npyi6pME4tkDNUDDZZCoPof8oNii46ApElfKb9eZgCfY/duhvuI93f8m9KpXbnuftxbn5XgvvcZSPY+mFX/a5f6W3ZcFxjttqLHESdceu6hEcOktVpT+9OronUBSrTXrtEUTLdTb2EK3WGpmrnF9s8oMY5Z0CoCBYiCBJiGeoQ9KKnMuUeExHQ4NfEIiW3moFB15eWm64d3gEzxfAkth0ky6mDI+6jI38crkmLvkjAkNX5CKmCKWK1qvOCTm3ntQaMXyActLMFZdC6fOtYRmSDTkbkC/xyuy6NWU6JQ4c8ObE1HLI292BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30wmFPnA7s5LW6Bk96msBinKOnn26K7mQ2wDGYxWWpYE5G8KKWIl5mGsG2v8h5vCTSPdfVMOf9yCB8+seDtgwKzZtZpU7W9du/vMwoZh59BpRQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7046","langCode":"vi","question":"TGIbieZrJvjf8QloQvExoSEEBhBelXudfZShMmlm4TNqrxX+wTlbf3eaRwSIC/9htIxbLiauwsbkMJQzCssIbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["with","by","about","from"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"f4YFPIuPXWr0TPKVanIUa6nQlmbuRmwCr5fWJYxWj9edsII3WVt6b82b8zQvo0UE9UXwAHxnW8eYbk/RIcfAAO0Ou+FEFNvKg79Ep/5HkiEs4Pd4n5Z8clNfzt01Q33dKfJqNyX9lsLx2rlcRSa+QIsRRa7Aftox017PTq2PwMr67TynijjbztU7kGAX69V+1ZkSsmeUo+Vj9RExRPw4pa9r9A9Fe4qbTX5RLTkxgyj/wyIFp7xx7KAhfsQCG4TXdUZ0kJ22TA8SOc41RCnnb6OSXRO9RiaAmjnvtRGa3CMwsfG+7sIXeQYdYgb/UFQ4swzFEVboFIhNvxoATyyV0WgLbBkl856ATL6Hn6ZUtYcRJvsk0Ir9K3CWX+lG0zJEuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuI/fsao+/gu7nLI5bP27G/ZJOzXVne+fx/BUJhztq6gUk/dhiXgnJptmbV4GmF1wynAu3Ww7eaUtRe2Fii8NUoIu1Yh0b9kCrMfpaE4x4eHNsb3xccuqnz+y4eWf98+8c9S7kQ2o37Jwy9EY1dqQWkd"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7047","langCode":"vi","question":"iTqmdKKFnxiei+ov94lF4Ff/jzKCIscMZHov8BW1h9o9QMKaVUV0z2zSv65VSfx4","answers":["of","by","with","for"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"UF4bdb/J1nh95W3QWXtRIz0Pg3uoMzgKF2v7xRLYZG8SolNHbfwmAa1HkYXNFKL4wLGQp8zG1MvFQJWyNn3nwDXlHaEicFmmI3KNVR6fQSCAblfuQ50BrTRpqeIShEyobaXAkFUlbTQV3R0mw4XRqoOBnSWKR0ncqZu5BoHkUaUwScBGbHF8sS06XVHlsgTpDG3fjzbeMOMfTFMcFG/NVpYZbX74vpFCDJzyiK3GgNo6WudsOda3ZX+s05XpbKFgpDURGP0V0FjBVu0hDYG7K2X/GFL/svu5JRE0llC5BjGClBdcqcMrj6f9ADUY6uiDMR1Shi6Z86U7g1qajORcJeRlr6pwjYZC/6CwGkU3nCI4DmkJYLAmapp5c/ovqr0Y88FjncdqbjgHROGTJc89m292BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30xsgJ2mXfwy7pvKP1LymbssWX7Q8xQHc9KBnL08+4v8ad4N0NKn75sKkgoK2zc7xfmi31obTGNKPSCCr2/1UmhsH1qotM6dYcH/f/KbpACwYA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7048","langCode":"vi","question":"2Iz75YL+El6fRBwt+QVpqcfh4qQrh5i6pjXHJIiVpvcODNBSi5aMCJS3rTaObSL9WN3fMGRTx9bzVaSoCh1fQuOsbYtEFsZXlmZ/i3l+YNM\u003d","answers":["against","at","by","since"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"0xaBQ71JeAAFJ4uBlDMh71VSMLGeWMUBoxYQI83/5iioCngeBrfxXje37fJrD4AxZVLX42V3lZTjvqA3+LtOL2/3Hg3sdpb+F/4KlDB6tCgZQYbH+w5m1A2DiQESqfM9WkIhD0ZFvUqTB8hziwYSYQ15FezzuOmDn6dCDp3x+1qnfhh/jz1YutS8Wefz9RSZKGQrL+DdquvQYT8W1y9ANM15yL5jMy9thm507A2Du0FEWejc46crg049r/Y07qvuk2OJqPieHLZC+BT1viqocLEO7k4qqQddLVzlpP1VMXP49MYujo8VXgBcQQRUyYi1lb8uAtx3/yYS6EGi7FFpvpDacNvxJVOHO9j8gh0GR8v1Yef50IRLcR6fG+eMfMhPbUJJackF6JbGzJx6o4sF9svLltcRPM9B5IfXEf3w7rh7KtSEGdtVqAvPYxQ3TE5mVazdsouMc0jJe/WA/KRRoef0/Dl9gn2KzapTcaZHFw3QQBgkx8lDYwl/ku5o7Z5FxT5mH6ZCD6th9ZaDz6BCpZNbDHNVLxcxX7t/hGt7Ax3W8d3pvgDFqzEo3CZEnA/QSUuJRI0rYlqzYXlMFHN3IGoqa8AbGB8UtS2sXgeMlAVUu7d8VkAngYNDVpoj1e+4RSfFLBNQ7wzROZdMuno4ZO6D1V9BsNKVF4braXaUzn1ivpzeOL2GZfbGMazqmyFuyrkDQR46QddigbnplYFsEezJUunnBSV0VTa+9olUMorjJdr9mAz4De46CRhMLNH2ElSc0wmU1EtlK6DQh7yX/spqeU5bURGcgKScvDSGT4Y\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7049","langCode":"vi","question":"jCZpefyKfbZNcp4+4ULh2IgSaWiY4Tfz3mzmgmGn3TsVwLpcYNNJ/FOFuIoigEcNNoXtMooLDWpip2UHMsEAVA\u003d\u003d","answers":["with ","among","after","at "],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"jawCda234k2EpQJWEW4RqCjwiSqJkgghiHSCskPErP+UFScl5DkyTof1CKzv1vVEb/ceDex2lv4X/gqUMHq0KBlBhsf7DmbUDYOJARKp8z1aQiEPRkW9SpMHyHOLBhJhJdNE0TcKnNsGSrU9owKYQlDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqEn43erjuCM5iA+TUdVvMVmK5J4sONiY2qVAQ8IFcmv0Km6nnrZJiOM9AXG/AGJNjDCW+VsV1F+VY0yI6jvjeQPNMVLYBG/ZcDFW8ZaxJ42Tl8bexrNxexFO3jjTBVUXYmVEJnTioiKNu70zIc8o5G6mQUxjFw2cFk5bYR63Aupqbt37xVymN8IhGWGxt45TBusH+lGw6kbYpiwAlKZABFuhZqrUZAIllbyYHrHJ9fa5Tmp3XAHKXERURDTiyvez/cixt3Uh6X6x0f7xp9Ztr7g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"7","id":"7050","langCode":"vi","question":"YOCJn95bw2LjNn294wlJhqFYQsCIG1lhZ0o2odg/6VbNc8+lQ2ESihnL06Hv5gfs3EX+Ia5gkEtL4bLZMwfehA\u003d\u003d","answers":["by","in","at","since "],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"vRUgoLDwxcU5LzCpDkJcY2EvIXC+qKlC7nJBSvEG86WHOCZUqCW+49mYQ9914pROCdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHufkabVxx/sSl3ufAxhgiYd6RHPOUwF736vFpNoukbbKwX3w6MKFXZhePJvaBkZ389g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2/QX16yGQQiVI97mHLzGtwSg9CnqQtn7eKsReHh+/f4GRa5rleKkPeqH8H2TUgmrX1U/xdQgcildVWpZF57addLYbWBrydpM2E7Uu6GSy3r+aKD4fmBST8TzKoTvueERZLKPx8mcrF6JoHhiWC/0LB89eK6InqFl276Q+8GF/WOZo2HKuV5+O+Ty95sKTJW+D4pYLKifYZcWgSnyiPgjWVSIkkor5Uhb5VKOqpZibhWZxriMU9HM74Bhc4Y4GA5NeyMELOgPquykmvJ+UcbE96YIoIwfVh1Xqs0hryi3YbuRhWIMPFSYJ34vyU8vGqtl8JhSXzm3BGPkeQ5jSAhzU7B6NQivvBbT3QoU6TBhbp+SA\u003d\u003d"}]